Online classes began to be popularized just a few decades ago.
仅仅几十年前，网络课程才开始普及。
They are advertised as a way for adults to finish their education and students to learn the material at their own pace—it is far more compatible with people’s busy schedules.
网络课程被宣传为一种途径，让成年人能够完成学业，让学生能够按自己的节奏学习课程内容——这种方式与人们繁忙的日程安排要契合得多。
But after being enrolled in an online course last fall semester, I came to realize online classes were merely a means to fulfil course requirements.
但去年秋季学期选修了一门网络课程之后，我逐渐意识到，网络课程只不过是满足课程要求的一种手段。
First of all, students lack the desire to learn, and they simply complete their assignments to receive credit for a passing grade rather than genuinely engage with the course material.
首先，学生缺乏学习的愿望，他们完成作业只是为了拿到及格成绩、获得学分，而不是真正投入地学习课程内容。
As online courses tend to have more than 100 students, most of the assignments are short and simple.
由于网络课程的学生往往超过100人，大部分作业都简短而容易。
They are not designed for students to interact with the material in depth but designed to be graded easily to accommodate such a large number of students.
这些作业的设计目的不是让学生与课程内容深入互动，而是便于评分，以适应如此庞大的学生规模。
Perhaps the biggest disadvantage of taking an online class is the absence of face-to-face interaction between the teacher and their students.
修读网络课程最大的弊端，或许在于老师和学生之间缺少面对面的互动。
Live sessions are infrequent and are often scheduled during the middle of the day when students have to attend other classes or work.
直播课次数很少，而且常常安排在中午前后，而这个时候学生得去上别的课或者去上班。
The office hours of the professor may also be during inconvenient times for many students.
教授的答疑时间也可能安排在许多学生不方便的时段。
Most interaction with the professor has to be through email, which is often impersonal.
与教授的互动大多只能借助电子邮件，而电子邮件往往缺乏人情味。
It is nearly impossible for students to build a relationship with their professor.
学生几乎不可能与教授建立起关系。
There is also little interaction amongst students.
学生之间的互动也很少。
It can be harder for students to create study groups and form relationships with their peers.
对学生来说，组建学习小组、与同学建立关系可能会更难。
Online classes also require either a computer or laptop and a reliable internet connection.
网络课程还需要一台台式电脑或笔记本电脑，以及稳定的网络连接。
Not all students have access to these types of resources, whether it is for financial or other reasons, and some students can be put at a disadvantage.
无论是出于经济原因还是其他原因，并非所有学生都能用上这类资源，有些学生可能会处于不利地位。
Offering online classes certainly helps students who would otherwise not be able to attend classroom sessions.
开设网络课程无疑能帮助那些原本无法到教室上课的学生。
However, online classes fail to provide a genuine education, with an emphasis on convenience rather than critical thinking.
然而，网络课程未能提供真正的教育，注重的是便利，而不是批判性思维。
We need restructured online classes in which students can have a learning experience that will actually provide quality education.
我们需要经过重构的网络课程，让学生能在其中获得一种学习体验，真正为他们带来优质的教育。